A Guide to the Office of the Dean of Students Office Administrative Files, 1968-1999
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Office of the Dean of Students Office Administrative Files 1968-1999
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-18/2/1.991
This collection consists of 14,000 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions apply to personally identifiable student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library in 1999 August.
Scope and Content Information
Topical files from Dean Robert T. Canevari's office, including the files of the V. Shamim Sisson, Associate Dean of Students; Michelle A. Samuels, Assistant Dean of Students and F. Aaron Laushway, Assistant Dean of Students. Included in the collections are audio tape interviews with University presidents and files on fraternities and sororities.
Arrangement
Series I: Dean of Students, Robert T. Canevari Boxes 1-9; Series II: Associate Dean of Students, V. Shamim Sisson Boxes 10-18; Series III: Assistant Dean of Students, Michelle A. Samuels Box 18-21; Series IV: Assistant Dean of Students, F. Aaron Laushway Box 22-34; Series V: Restricted Files Box 35
Contents List
- Series I: Dean of Students,Robert T. Canevari
  - DOS Budget 1995-1996 (Box 1)
  - ODOS Program Budget 1995-1996 (Box 1)
  - 1-10830 DATS Account Info 1995-1996 (Box 1)
  - Gus Blagden Committee 1995-1996 (Box 1)
  - First Year Enrollment 1995-1996 (Box 1)
  - Dean of Students Miscellaneous 1996-1997 (Box 1)
  - Dean of Students Retreat 1996 (Box 1)
  - Melissa E. Salva, Intern 1996-1997 (Box 1)
  - Eating and Exercise Habits Committee 1995-1996 (Box 1)
  - Lawn Selection 1995-1996 (Box 1)
  - Room Assignment Ad Hoc Committee 1991 (Box 2)
  - Public Occasions 1993-1995 (Box 2)
  - Woody Report 1968 (Box 2)
  - Board of Visitors 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Discretionary Fund 1982-1988 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Association Discretionary Fund 1987-1991 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Discretionary Account 1993-1995 (Box 2)
  - ODOS - Alumni Association Discretionary Fund 1991-1993 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Association (History of) 1983-1985 (Box 2)
  - University Committee for 100th Anniversary of Rotunda Fire 1994-1996 (Box 2)
  - Duke University Assessment of Student Life 1993 (Box 2)
  - UVa Self Study: Compliance Audit Report 1994-1995 (Box 3)
  - VP Committee on U(niversity) U(nion) & S(tudent) A(ctivities) B(oard) 1995-1996 (Box 3)
  - Newcomb Hall Budget 1995-1996 (Box 3)
  - Charlottesville/Albemarle Miscellaneous 1986-1995 (Box 3)
  - University Staff Recognition Day Committee 1996 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association Miscellaneous 1996 (Box 3)
  - Arts and Sciences, Advisory Equipment 1996 (Box 3)
  - Athletic Department 1994-1996 (Box 3)
  - President's Retreat and Parents' Weekend 1995-1996 (Box 3)
  - Board of Visitors - Disruption 1986-1990 (Box 3)
  - Black Student Concerns 1994 (Box 4)
  - Gray/Carrington 1995-1996 (Box 4)
  - Canevari's Tales Project 1995 (Box 4)
  - Dean Canevari's Speeches 1994-1996 (Box 4)
  - ODOS/OAAA Interest Groups 1996 (Box 4)
  - Deans of Students 1991-1993 (Box 4)
  - Engineering, School of 1988-1993 (Box 4)
  - University Self Study 1995 (Box 4)
  - Search Committee (Assistant Dean of Students, Residence Life) 1996 (Box 4)
  - Fine Arts at UVa (Miscellaneous) 1991-1995 (Box 4)
  - Gay Student/Staff Study: Report on the survey of University of Virginia students, faculty and staff and staff on the environment for gays, lesbians, and bisexuals. 1994 (Box 4)
  - Judicial Advisor (ODOS Reports) 1982-1996 (Box 4)
  - Faculty/Staff Campaign 1995-1996 (Box 5)
  - Greek Endowment Scholarship Fund 1988 (Box 5)
  - Institute for Substance Abuse Studies 1992-1995 (Box 5)
  - Interfraternity Council 1996-1997 (Box 5)
  - Leadership Council 1996 (Box 5)
  - Longitudinal Study of Undergraduate Education (RTC) 1989-1992 (Box 5)
  - Lower Lawn Reservation Requests 1996-1997 (Box 5)
  - Multiculturalism 1989-1993 (Box 5)
  - Master's Degree Program 1992 (Box 5)
  - Arts Panel Project 1996 (Box 5)
  - Newcomb Construction 1995 (Box 5)
  - Newcomb Hall -- Large Multipurpose Space Report 1995 (Box 5)
  - Facilities Coordinator 1991-1996 (Box 5)
  - UVa 101 Proposal 1996 (Box 5)
  - Parents' Program and Reports 1995-1996 (Box 6)
  - Parents' Fund 1995-1996 (Box 6)
  - Culturefest 1995 (Box 6)
  - Department of Parking and Transportation 1989-1996 (Box 6)
  - Physical Plant 1991-1995 (Box 6)
  - Physical Violence 1992 (Box 6)
  - Assessment: First Year Survey (Residential Colleges) 1994 (Box 6)
  - President's Retreat 1995 (Box 6)
  - Registrar -- Finals Program Meetings 1995 (Box 6)
  - Provost Office 1992-1995 (Box 6)
  - Religion 1990-1996 (Box 6)
  - Resident Staff 1995-1996 (Box 6)
  - Substance Abuse Studies Council 1995-1997 (Box 6)
  - Newcomb Director's Office 1995-1997 (Box 7)
  - Newspaper Articles (Miscellaneous) 1996-1997 (Box 7)
  - O'Hill Dining -- Illegal Entries 1996 (Box 7)
  - Residence Life Office 1995-1996 (Box 7)
  - Robert T. Canevari Award 1995 (Box 7)
  - Recommendations (other than students) 1994-1996 (Box 7)
  - Comprehensive Plan for Residential Life 1986 (Box 7)
  - Residence Staff Serious Incident Reports 1995-1996 (Box 7)
  - North Grounds Residential College Proposal 1994 (Box 7)
  - SCHEV - misc. 1992-1995 (Box 7)
  - Student Self Governance 1989-1992 (Box 8)
  - Student Legal Services 1987-1991 (Box 8)
  - Student Legal Services (restricted) 1987-1991 (Box 8)
  - VPSA Staff Meetings (2 of 2) 1995-1996 (Box 8)
  - VPSA Staff Meetings (2 of 2) 1996-1997 (Box 8)
  - William Harmon, VP for Student Affairs 1995-1996 (Box 8)
  - Office of Afro-American Affairs 1991-1996 (Box 8)
  - Counseling Center 1990-1995 (Box 8)
  - University Journal 1986-1996 (Box 8)
  - Honor Committee 1995-1996 (Box 8)
  - Judiciary Committee 1995-1996 (Box 9)
  - DOS v. Sigma Phi Epsilon & Delta Zeta 1995 (Box 9)
  - Student Organizations (misc) 1995-1996 (Box 9)
  - Student Council 1995-1996 (Box 9)
  - Summer Session 1984-1995 (Box 9)
  - University Police 1994-1995 (Box 9)
  - University Union 1995-1996 (Box 9)
  - WTJU Radio 1995-1996 (Box 9)
  - WUVA, Inc. 1985-1996 (Box 9)
  - Stillfried/Godsey Scholarship 1995-1996 (Box 9)
  - "Interview with Four Presidents of the University of Virginia," an oral history project by Lisa Guernsey, Intern, Dean of Students Office 1993 (Box 9)
  - Audio Tape: Interview of C Titus and R Canevari, 10/26/95 Johnstone 1995 (Box 9)
- Series II: Associate Dean of Students, V. Shamim Sisson
  - Academic Support Cluster Group 1994 (Box 10)
  - African American Video Facilitator's Evaluation Submitted 1992-1993 (Box 10)
  - African American Student Experience at UVa Program (2 of 2) 1990-1992 (Box 10)
  - Biennial Evaluation and Planning 1988-1993 (Box 10)
  - Budget 1992-1993 (Box 10)
  - Cults 1984-1991 (Box 10)
  - Current Exit Interviews Originals (1 of 2) 1995 (Box 10)
  - Current Exit Interviews Originals (2 of 2) 1995 (Box 11)
  - Dean of Students -- General 1993-1997 (Box 11)
  - Dean of Students Memos 1992-1994 (Box 11)
  - Faculty Reimbursements 1995 (Box 11)
  - Family Weekend Sign-in sheets 1995 (Box 11)
  - Family Weekend Brochure 1996 (Box 11)
  - Family Weekend Sign-in Sheets 1996 (Box 11)
  - Family Weekend Brochure 1996 (Box 11)
  - Parents' Weekend Survey 1996 (Box 11)
  - Family Weekend (2 of 2) 1996 (Box 11)
  - Family Weekend -- Key Documents 1996 (Box 12)
  - Family Weekend -- Qualitative Data 1996 (Box 12)
  - Family Weekend Survey 1996 (Box 12)
  - Family Weekend Follow-up 1997 (Box 12)
  - Changes/Additions to Family Weekend Brochure 1997 (Box 12)
  - Family Weekend 1998 (Box 12)
  - Family Weekend Brochure 1997 (Box 12)
  - FYS Development Project 1992-1995 (Box 12)
  - First Year Seminar 1995-1996 (Box 12)
  - First Year Seminar 1996-1997 (Box 13)
  - First Year Seminar 1998 (Box 13)
  - FYS Exit Interviews 1998 (Box 13)
  - FYS Participant Evaluations 1998 (Box 13)
  - Incentive Pay Plan 1993 (Box 13)
  - First Year Seminar 1997-1998 (Box 13)
  - FYS Applicants 1997 (Box 13)
  - First Year Seminar 1997 (Box 13)
  - Completed Applications 1998 (Box 13)
  - JPA Neighborhood - Pending 1993-1995 (Box 13)
  - Student Leadership Functions: University-Wide 1992-1995 (Box 13)
  - Leadership 2000 Assessment 1995 (Box 13)
  - Leadership 2000 Operations 1995-1996 (Box 13)
  - Leadership 2000 Program 1995 (Box 13)
  - Leadership 2000 1996 (Box 13)
  - Evaluations: Leadership 2000 1996 (Box 13)
  - Leadership 2000 Summer Rental 1996 (Box 14)
  - Leadership 2000 Operations 1996 (Box 14)
  - Leadership 2000 Evaluations 1997 (Box 14)
  - Leadership 2000 1997 (Box 14)
  - Leadership 2000 Operations 1997 (Box 14)
  - Leadership 2000 1998 (Box 14)
  - NCAA Alcohol Task Force 1990-1993 (Box 14)
  - ODOS Assessment Project: General (3 of 3) 1993-1994 (Box 15)
  - ODOS Assessment Project: Instruments 1993-1994 (Box 15)
  - ODOS Assessment -- General (2 of 2) 1995-1996 (Box 15)
  - ODOS Assessment -- General 1995-1996 (Box 16)
  - Fourth Year Participation Survey 1996 (Box 16)
  - ODOS Assessment -- General (2 of 2) 1996-1997 (Box 16)
  - Returned ODOS Assessment Surveys -- Suggested Revisions 1997 (Box 16)
  - Pep Band Review Board 1991-1994 (Box 16)
  - Pep Band Review Committee: Origination and Correspondence 1987-1995 (Box 16)
  - Phi Eta Sigma 1993-1995 (Box 16)
  - WLDP (Women's Leadership Development Program) 1995 (Box 16)
  - WLDP Budget 1995-1996 (Box 16)
  - WLDP Catering 1995-1996 (Box 16)
  - WLDP Keynote and Panelist 1995-1996 (Box 17)
  - Women's Leadership Development Program -- Meetings Feb-March 1996 (Box 17)
  - WLDP Agendas and Meetings 1995-1996 (Box 17)
  - WLDP Mentor List & Mentee List 1995-1996 (Box 17)
  - WLDP Program Participants 1995-1996 (Box 17)
  - WLDP: Organization List to send for student nominations 1995-1996 (Box 17)
  - WLDP: Mentorship Internship Program 1995-1996 (Box 17)
  - WLDP: Form Letters 1995-1996 (Box 17)
  - WLDP: Programs for Events 1995-1996 (Box 17)
  - Participant List 1997 (Box 17)
  - Women's Leadership 1995-1996 (Box 17)
  - WLDP Room Reservations 1995-1996 (Box 17)
  - WLDP Surveys 1995-1996 (Box 17)
  - Womens' Leadership Development Members 1995 (Box 17)
  - Phi Eta Sigma 1995-1997 (Box 17)
  - WLDP -- Nominee List 1995-1996 (Box 17)
  - WLDP Timeline 1995-1995 (Box 17)
  - WLDP: Agendas and Minutes 1996-1997 (Box 17)
  - WLDP: Budgets and Expenses 1996-1997 (Box 17)
  - WLDP: Committee Members 1996-1997 (Box 18)
  - WLDP: Mentors/Mentees 1996-1997 (Box 18)
  - WLDP: Session 1 Feb 1 1997 (Box 18)
  - WLDP: Session 2 Mar 2 1997 (Box 18)
  - Final Dinner Mar 26 1997 (Box 18)
  - WLDP: Surveys 1996-1997 (Box 18)
  - Form Letters 1996-1997 (Box 18)
  - Women's Leadership Development Program - Overview 1997 (Box 18)
- Series III: Assistant Dean of Students, Michelle A. Samuels
  - African American Leadership Association 1996 (Box 18)
  - 1st African American High School Leadership Conference 1995 (Box 18)
  - African American Leadership 2nd Annual High School Conference 1996 (Box 18)
  - 2nd African American Leadership Conference Materials 1995 (Box 18)
  - African American Student Leadership Seminar 1994 (Box 18)
  - Building Linkages 1995-1996 (Box 19)
  - Building Linkages 1996-1997 (Box 19)
  - CIO Agreement Revision 1993-1994 (Box 19)
  - CIO Printing Vouchers 1992 (Box 19)
  - Cultural Connectors 1995-1996 (Box 19)
  - Faculty Reimbursement Fund 1996-1997 (Box 19)
  - Faculty Reimbursement Fund 1997 (Box 19)
  - Faculty Reimbursement Year End Reports 1993 (Box 19)
  - Faculty Reimbursement Fund Monthly Reports 1996-1997 (Box 19)
  - Facilitators for Orientation 1995 (Box 19)
  - Fall Convocation 1993 (Box 19)
  - Fall Convocation 1994 (Box 19)
  - First Year Resource Center 1998 (Box 19)
  - Survey of First Year Students 1995 (Box 19)
  - Leadership 2000 1992 (Box 19)
  - Leadership 2000 1993 (Box 19)
  - Leadership 2000 1994 (Box 19)
  - Leadership 2000 1995 (Box 19)
  - Leadership 2000 1997 (Box 19)
  - Miscellaneous 1997 (Box 20)
  - Oasis 1994 (Box 20)
  - Oasis - Parents' Reception Responses 1994 (Box 20)
  - Oasis 1995 (Box 20)
  - Oasis 1996 (Box 20)
  - Oasis 1997 (Box 20)
  - Orientation Brochures 1997 (Box 20)
  - Orientation Brochures First Set 1997 (Box 20)
  - Orientation Correspondence 1997 (Box 20)
  - Academic Programs 1997 (Box 20)
  - Facilities 1997 (Box 20)
  - Orientation Taskforce 1997 (Box 20)
  - Orientation -- JMU 1997-1998 (Box 20)
  - Residence Life 1997 (Box 20)
  - Orientation Evaluations 1996 (Box 20)
  - Schedules 1996-1997 (Box 20)
  - Social Programming 1997 (Box 20)
  - Student Life 1997 (Box 20)
  - Student Orientation Review Committee 1997 (Box 21)
  - Supplemental Programs 1997 (Box 21)
  - Parents' Fund Requests 1992 (Box 21)
  - Parents' Fund Requests 1993 (Box 21)
  - Parents' Fund 1990-1992 (Box 21)
  - Parents' Program 1994 (Box 21)
  - Parents' Fund Program 1996 (Box 21)
  - Parents' Program 1996-1997 (Box 21)
  - Schedule for Parents' Weekend and Homecoming 1995-1998 (Box 21)
  - President's Convocation 1994 (Box 21)
  - President's Convocation 1995 (Box 21)
  - President's Convocation 1996 (Box 21)
  - President's Welcome Letter 1994 (Box 21)
  - SERVE 1997 (Box 21)
  - SERVE Project Evaluations 1997 (Box 21)
  - SERVE Planning 1997 (Box 21)
- Series IV: Assistant Dean of Students, F. Aaron Laushway
  - Aaron Laushway: Interim Assistant Dean 1997-1998 (Box 22)
  - "An Added Dimension" for Students Who Transferred 1993-1994 (Box 22)
  - BFC: Group Advisors 1993-1995 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence: Theresa Carroll/Michelle Ritter 1993-1996 (Box 22)
  - Council of Community 1993-1994 (Box 22)
  - Exit Interviews 1996 (Box 22)
  - FOA Program Resource Guide 1995-1996 (Box 22)
  - FOA Report Forms 1995-1996 (Box 22)
  - FOAs - Graduate Assistants 1994-1996 (Box 22)
  - FAC Maintenance Fund 1991-1996 (Box 22)
  - Federal and National Community Service Programs 1994 (Box 22)
  - General Correspondence 1993-1995 (Box 22)
  - First Year Council 1995 (Box 22)
  - Fraternity Alumni Council 1993 (Box 22)
  - Fraternity/Sorority Party Patrol 1994-1995 (Box 22)
  - Fraternity/Sorority Police Meetings 1995 (Box 22)
  - GOALS 1992 (Box 22)
  - Glee Club 1993 (Box 22)
  - Goals and Objectives 1986-1987 (Box 22)
  - Goals and Objectives 1988-1991 (Box 22)
  - Graduate Assistant 1994-1995 (Box 23)
  - Graffiti 1990 (Box 23)
  - Greek Coordinating Committee 1995-1996 (Box 23)
  - IFC Miscellaneous 1995-1996 (Box 23)
  - IFC/ISC/BFC Paintball 1991 (Box 23)
  - ISC Miscellaneous 1995-1996 (Box 23)
  - Karen Blum 1998 (Box 23)
  - NIC (National Interfraternity Conference) 1995-1996 (Box 23)
  - Native American Resources Within Virginia 1993-1994 (Box 23)
  - Native American Student Organizations 1994 (Box 23)
  - New President Meetings 1996 (Box 23)
  - NT-TSPA Program 1995-1996 (Box 23)
  - NT-TSPA Program 1996-1997 (Box 23)
  - OASIS - TSPA Program 1993 (Box 23)
  - S.E.R.V.E 1996 (Box 23)
  - Strength Deployment Inventory 1994-1995 (Box 23)
  - Student Affairs Deans in Schools and Colleges 1991 (Box 23)
  - Student Assistant Mentor Program 1995 (Box 23)
  - Transfer Student Survey 1995-1996 (Box 23)
  - Transfer Students Mid Year Orientation 1992-1995 (Box 24)
  - TSPA Orientation Fair 1993-1994 (Box 24)
  - TSPA Program 1995-1996 (Box 24)
  - TSPA Program 1996-1997 (Box 24)
  - UVA Cares - Exercise and Eating 1995 (Box 24)
  - UVA Lead (2 of 2) 1997-1998 (Box 24)
  - On Target Weekly Meetings 1990-1991 (Box 24)
  - On Target Retreat 1991 (Box 24)
  - On Target Retreat 1992 (Box 24)
  - On Target Retreat Jan-93 (Box 24)
  - On Target Retreat Fall 1993 (Box 24)
  - Seminar and Timelines - On Target 1989-1990 (Box 24)
  - On Target Retreat Fall 1994 (Box 24)
  - Special Events Risk Management - Planning Guide n.d. (Box 24)
  - On Target - Committee Retreat 1989-1990 (Box 24)
  - OT - High School Leadership Program 1992 (Box 24)
  - On Target Retreat 1990 (Box 25)
  - The Assemblage 1989-1990 (Box 25)
  - The Assemblage 1990-1991 (Box 25)
  - Assemblage II: An Experience for High School Leaders 3/13/1991 (Box 25)
  - On Target CIO Survey Results 1994 (Box 25)
  - On Target Survey 1990-1999 (Box 25)
  - On Target Programming - Extra Cover Pages 1988-1989 (Box 25)
  - Alpha Chi Omega 1993-1995 (Box 25)
  - Fraternity -- Alpha Delta Phi 1993-1995 (Box 25)
  - Fraternity -- Alpha Epsilon Pi 1993-1995 (Box 25)
  - Alpha Kappa Alpha 1993-1995 (Box 25)
  - Alpha Delta Pi 1993-1995 (Box 25)
  - Fraternity -- Alpha Tau Omega 1993-1995 (Box 25)
  - Fraternity -- Beta Theta Pi 1993-1995 (Box 25)
  - Chi Omega 1993-1995 (Box 25)
  - Fraternity -- Chi Phi (2 of 2) 1993-1995 (Box 25)
  - Fraternity -- Chi Psi 1993-1995 (Box 25)
  - Delta Delta Delta 1993-1995 (Box 25)
  - Delta Gamma 1993-1995 (Box 25)
  - Fraternity -- Delta Kappa Epsilon 1993-1995 (Box 26)
  - Fraternity -- Delta Sigma Phi 1993-1995 (Box 26)
  - Delta Sigma Theta 1993-1995 (Box 26)
  - Fraternity -- Delta Tau Delta 1993-1995 (Box 26)
  - Fraternity - Delta Upsilon 1993-1995 (Box 26)
  - Delta Zeta 1993-1995 (Box 26)
  - Gamma Phi Beta 1993-1995 (Box 26)
  - Fraternity -- Kappa Alpha 1993-1995 (Box 26)
  - Fraternity -- Kappa Alpha 1993-1995 (Box 26)
  - Kappa Alpha Theta 1993-1995 (Box 26)
  - Kappa Delta 1993-1995 (Box 26)
  - Fraternity -- Phi Beta Sigma 1993-1995 (Box 26)
  - Fraternity -- Omega Psi Phi (Restricted) 1993-1995 (Box 26)
  - Fraternity -- Phi Delta Theta 1993-1995 (Box 26)
  - Fraternity -- Phi Gamma Delta 1993-1995 (Box 26)
  - Fraternity -- Sigma Nu 1993-1995 (Box 26)
  - Fraternity -- Phi Kappa Psi 1993-1995 (Box 26)
  - Fraternity -- Phi Kappa Sigma 1990-1993 (Box 26)
  - Fraternity -- Phi Kappa Sigma 1993-1995 (Box 27)
  - Phi Mu 1993-1995 (Box 27)
  - Fraternity -- Phi Sigma Kappa 1993-1995 (Box 27)
  - Pi Beta Phi 1993-1995 (Box 27)
  - Fraternity -- Pi Kappa Alpha 1993-1995 (Box 27)
  - Pi Kappa Phi 1993-1995 (Box 27)
  - Fraternity -- Pi Lambda Phi 1993-1995 (Box 27)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon 1993-1995 (Box 27)
  - Fraternity -- Sigma Alpha Mu 1993-1995 (Box 27)
  - Fraternity -- Sigma Chi 1993-1995 (Box 27)
  - Sigma Gamma Rho 1993-1995 (Box 27)
  - Sigma Kappa 1993-1995 (Box 27)
  - Fraternity -- Sigma Phi 1993-1995 (Box 27)
  - Fraternity -- Sigma Pi 1993-1995 (Box 27)
  - Sigma Sigma Sigma 1993-1995 (Box 28)
  - Fraternity -- Saint Elmo Hall 1993-1995 (Box 28)
  - Fraternity -- Theta Chi 1993-1995 (Box 28)
  - Fraternity -- Theta Delta Chi 1993-1995 (Box 28)
  - Fraternity -- Zeta Beta Tau 1993-1995 (Box 28)
  - Zeta Phi Beta 1993-1995 (Box 28)
  - Fraternity -- Zeta Psi 1993-1995 (Box 28)
  - Zeta Tau Alpha 1993-1995 (Box 28)
  - Alpha Kappa Alpha 1994-1995 (Box 28)
  - Delta Sigma Theta 1994-1996 (Box 28)
  - Kappa Alpha Psi 1995-1996 (Box 28)
  - Omega Psi Phi 1994-1996 (Box 28)
  - Sigma Gamma Rho 1994-1996 (Box 28)
  - Zeta Phi Beta 1994-1996 (Box 28)
  - Alpha Delta Phi 1994-1997 (Box 28)
  - Alpha Epsilon Pi 1994-1997 (Box 28)
  - Alpha Tau Omega 1994-1997 (Box 28)
  - Beta Theta Pi 1994-1997 (Box 28)
  - Chi Phi 1994-1997 (Box 29)
  - Chi Psi 1994-1997 (Box 29)
  - Chi Psi 1994-1997 (Box 29)
  - Delta Sigma Phi 1994-1997 (Box 29)
  - Delta Tau Delta 1994-1997 (Box 29)
  - Delta Upsilon 1994-1997 (Box 29)
  - Kappa Alpha 1994-1997 (Box 29)
  - Kappa Sigma 1994-1997 (Box 29)
  - Kappa Sigma 1993-1995 (Box 29)
  - Phi Delta Theta 1994-1997 (Box 29)
  - Phi Gamma Delta 1994-1997 (Box 30)
  - Phi Kappa Psi 1994-1997 (Box 30)
  - Phi Kappa Sigma 1994-1997 (Box 30)
  - Phi Sigma Kappa 1994-1997 (Box 30)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha 1994-1997 (Box 30)
  - Phi Kappa Phi 1994-1997 (Box 30)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon 1994-1997 (Box 30)
  - Sigma Alpha Mu 1994-1997 (Box 31)
  - Sigma Chi 1994-1997 (Box 31)
  - Sigma Nu 1994-1997 (Box 31)
  - Sigma Phi 1994-1997 (Box 31)
  - Sigma Phi Epsilon 1993-1995 (Box 31)
  - Sigma Phi Epsilon 1994-1997 (Box 31)
  - Sigma Pi 1994-1997 (Box 31)
  - St. Anthony Hall 1994-1997 (Box 31)
  - Theta Chi 1994-1997 (Box 32)
  - Theta Delta Chi 1994-1997 (Box 32)
  - Zeta Beta Tau 1994-1997 (Box 32)
  - Zeta Psi 1994-1997 (Box 32)
  - Zeta Psi 1994-1997 (Box 32)
  - Alpha Delta Pi 1994-1997 (Box 32)
  - Alpha Phi 1994-1997 (Box 32)
  - Chi Omega 1994-1997 (Box 33)
  - Delta Delta Delta 1994-1997 (Box 33)
  - Delta Gamma 1994-1997 (Box 33)
  - Delta Zeta 1994-1997 (Box 33)
  - Gamma Phi Beta 1994-1997 (Box 33)
  - Kappa Alpha Theta 1994-1997 (Box 33)
  - Kappa Delta 1994-1997 (Box 33)
  - Kappa Kappa Gamma 1993-1995 (Box 33)
  - Kappa Kappa Gamma 1994-1997 (Box 34)
  - Phi Mu 1994-1997 (Box 34)
  - Phi Beta Pi 1994-1997 (Box 34)
  - Sigma Kappa 1994-1997 (Box 34)
  - Sigma Sigma Sigma 1994-1997 (Box 34)
  - Zeta Tau Beta 1994-1997 (Box 34)
- Series V: Restricted Files